Lauren Waknin

Full Stack Developer

Tel Aviv | 054-259-7679 | <u>laurenwaknin27@gmail.com</u> GitHub | <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>personal portfolio/website URL/blog url</u>

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in JavaScript based programming currently majoring in Computer Science. Determined and solution-oriented with a diverse portfolio of academic and professional experiences.

Highly autonomous but also adept in team environments and in motivating others. I have a strong passion for technology, innovation and sustainability. Outside of work, I am a motorcycle enthusiast, a Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu hobbyist and an amateur photographer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, PostgreSQL, React.js

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Riding Buddies App - Github | Demo (add hyperlinks)

Brief description of the app's functionality and purpose

- Utilized JSON Web Tokens to store encrypted user information client-side.
- Languages used: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, React

Coin Game - Github | Demo (add hyperlinks)

Brief description of the app's functionality and purpose

- Utilized p5.js library to create game character and background
- Languages used: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Budget App - Github | Demo (add hyperlinks)

Brief description of the app's functionality and purpose

- Utilized localStorage to store user information client-side.
- Languages used: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, React

EXPERIENCE

External Affairs Executive

Tel Aviv, Israel 09/2021 – 05/2022

Philip Morris Ltd

Finance: managed grant requests / approvals; assisted in managing corporate affairs and communications budget

- Procurement: created purchase requisitions; coordinated with vendors; validated invoices; managed account
 payables
- Logistics: Organized events; scheduled event halls; coordinated with staff to optimize availability; dealt with unexpected issues
- Communications & Public Relations: contributed to corporate communication campaigns; supported external communication's tasks such as earned, owned & paid media initiatives; responded to external requests from media or designated appropriate representative

Executive Assistant to Sr Counsel / Office Manager

Philip Morris Ltd

Tel Aviv, Israel 05/2017 - 09/2021

- Scheduling: managed the senior counsels schedule, travel arrangements & logistics
- Procurement: responsible for preparing and reconciling expenses, creating purchase requisitions, & effecting good receipt
- Vendor Management: in charge of opening new vendors and handled the contract repository with a high degree of confidentiality
- **Customer Engagement:** responsible for customer engagement pertaining to user dissatisfaction; empathized with customers to understand pain points; settled/forwarded cases on an ad hoc basis

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Tel Aviv, Israel 10/2022 - 12/2022

Computer Science London, United Kindgdom

Goldsmiths, University of London Present

Automotive Mechanics Montreal, Canada West Island Career Center

09/2015

LANGUAGES

English - native speaker French - native speaker **Hebrew** - fluent